<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Maryam Khezrzadeh</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Maryam Khezrzadeh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Future of Work</title>
      <link>/post/future-of-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/future-of-work/</guid>
      <description>We are all working these days, man and woman. And it seems like we are all wondering: how could work be better? How could it be more meaningful and satisfying? How could it be less tiring and more aligned with who we really are. And beyond that, how could we become who we are through our work?
 This third episode of the podcast is about the future of work, which as you can imagine is closely related to the future of cities and the future of economy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fear, Anxiety, Action!</title>
      <link>/post/fear-anxiety-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/fear-anxiety-action/</guid>
      <description>I shared the last post about why to write with a couple of friends, hoping that it wouldn’t bore them. It didn’t! And they wrote back to me.
 I first heard from Heather: “What do you think is the fear that underlies the anxiety?” She asked. When I read the question, I almost cringed. I had mixed feelings about the question and I was surprised to feel that way. So I dug some more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Write</title>
      <link>/post/why-write/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/why-write/</guid>
      <description>I talk a lot sometimes. I may keep going on and on, to the point of annoying whoever that might be listening.
I’ve noticed that my talking-too-much and my feeling-anxious are related. That is, if I have too many conversations, I generally become a more anxious version of me, and, if I’m anxious I generally talk more. It can be a devastating loop!
Too Much Talk Makes me Anxious Words have a way of capturing my attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Enterprises</title>
      <link>/post/social-enterprises/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/social-enterprises/</guid>
      <description>I’ve frequently talked about this one store in our neighbourhood that I really like. The reasons I like it go beyond good prices and the fact that it offers non-toxic products and soap refilling.
The people here are good. And they are doing something important. So I decided to have a conversation with Elizabeth, the founder of Second Nature and I really hope you enjoy listening to it.
This is only the second episode of Ten Minute Conversations and I really hope that you get a chance to send along your feedback on the podcast, either in person or on the digital :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Visible Mosaic</title>
      <link>/post/the-visible-mosaic/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-visible-mosaic/</guid>
      <description> There are thousands of NGOs (None-Govermental Organization) and CSOs (Civil Society Organization) in BC. What are these organizations working on? How are they related? What can we learn from the current state of affairs, so we can amplify the positive things that are happening and we minimize the damage from the negative forces that are affecting our lives?
 Read the Article  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Future of Technology</title>
      <link>/post/the-future-of-technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-future-of-technology/</guid>
      <description> A couple of months back, I asked Todd Sieling of Denim&amp;amp;Steel: “What is in the future of tech?”. Our initial conversation was very interesting so I followed up and asked the same question one more time. The result is a ten minute conversation that would challenge the dominant stories we often hear about the role of technology in our future.
 Read the Article Listen to the Conversation   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plastic Fashion</title>
      <link>/post/plastic-fashion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/plastic-fashion/</guid>
      <description> Fashion industry is a top contributor to climate change. Moreover, a lack of transparency in the fashion supply chain, makes a fertile soil for modern slavery to grow. In this study I compare two groups of fashion brands. I look for indicators that would tell us if these brands are doing the right thing to address the environmental and social issues associated with their businesses.
 Read the Article  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toxic Beauty</title>
      <link>/post/toxic-beauty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/toxic-beauty/</guid>
      <description> Toxic Beauty is an investigation into the use of harmful chemicals in beauty and personal care products. In this study, I analyze ingredients used by 1600 different brands. The analysis reveals a particular landscape of the beauty industry and is an invitation to know more and to choose wiser.
 Read the Article  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>